Someone, help!
Help! Help me!
Th-They're going to kill me!
Are you an adventurer?
P-Please help me!
Let me handle this.
What?
Can you really take them?
Are you actually a famous
adventurer despite how you look?
No.
What?!
I just leveled up
for the first time in my life.
Y-You're hopeless!
You're way weaker than me!
A newbie can't handle that many monsters.
And take off that heavy armor!
We have to run!
Rampart Reflection isn't perfect.
Unless you negate all damage
with a defense vastly superior
to your opponent's attack,
it doesn't activate.
Run!
It's ineffective against superior
and unknown enemies.
But...
Rampart Reflection!
What?!
Defense
I'm already familiar with starter enemies.
And I boosted my defense with
skill tree bonuses and equipment.
When it comes to fighting Raana...
I can beat dozens of them!
What?!
You beat that many Raana? Wh-Who are you?
I'm Elymas Edvau...
This is exactly what you deserve!
Don't show your face here again!
Don't use the Edvaughn family name
outside these walls.
If you do, I'll have your head!
Sorry.
No...
I'm Elymas the Heavy Knight.
Loading
Begin Adventure
Episode 2\h\h\h\h\h\hMenacing Foul Eight-Legged Beast
Level 8 reached.
"Unwavering One" title acquired
"Unwavering One" title has been acquired.
Display stats.
Class: Heavy Knight
Elymas Edvaughn
Attack
Defense
Magic
Speed
It seems safe to assume this world's
systems work just like Magic World's.
Equipment
Skills
Grunt Sword
Rampart Reflection
Iron Armor
Titles
Unwavering One
Elymas.
My name's Arus.
I left my backwater village
to become an adventurer, but...
Hey, wait.
I was told I couldn't be trusted
unless I reached level 3 on my own.
I was panicking since
I couldn't get into a party.
You saved my neck.
Let me thank you.
Don't worry about it.
What?
That was perfect for grinding levels.
I'll be taking
all the Magic Stones, though.
Yeah, sure. Of course.
Hey, Elymas, what say we form
a party when we get back?
I've got a lead.
You must be struggling
to find work by yourself, too.
Defensive classes aren't popular.
Heavy Knight? What's the meaning of this?!
With low stats across the board
and no decent attack skills, it's useless!
Without a doubt, it's a defective class!
Father, please calm down.
It has the highest HP and defense.
I don't care about that!
But I think you're amazing.
I think we'd be great together.
I promise I'll change
the others' minds, too.
Nah, I'm good.
What? But why?
That was a shield class
fighting style, right?
You'll never level up if you go it alone.
Don't be stubborn.
Sorry.
Arus is right.
Normally, defensive classes are best
when they're drawing enemy attacks
and protecting allies.
But if I drag along a bunch of allies,
I'll have to share EXP.
That sucks for the way I want to level.
Unwavering One
Skill Book
I'd like to gain items,
skills, and titles, too.
I'm not even sure anyone
will believe what I say.
Besides...
I don't have time to waste here.
There's still so much I have to do
to become a truly strong Heavy Knight.
C'mon, Elymas.
I'm saying this for your sake.
You're amazing, but your current
method will only get you so far.
There's no point in farming
Raana forever, right?
Let's aim higher together.
N-No way! What's this doing here?!
Display stats!
Monster:\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hAriandype
An Ariandype.
It's double my current level.
It was using its
Creepy-Crawly skill to hide.
It's got slowing poison
and the Flaming Claw skill, too.
Rampart Reflection is practically useless
against higher-level enemies.
Without a defense equal to
double their attack, it won't activate.
If I eat Flaming Claw, it'll one-shot me.
Damn it. This is my fault.
I lured it to us.
I-I'll keep it busy while you run.
I... I... I...
No, it's okay.
I'll do it. Let me handle it.
Hey, wait!
You're out of your mind.
No...
What?
This battle...
isn't unwinnable!
There's nothing newbies can do
to beat an Ariandype!
Elymas, I know you're amazing,
but it's physically impossible!
Display stats.
Magic
Speed
Equipment
Grunt Sword
Iron Armor
Skills
Rampart Reflection
Titles
Unwavering One
I've got the seven skill points
I gained earlier.
Skill Points:
I'll put all of them into
Oath of the Heavy Armor!
Disarm [Common Skill]
Temporarily reduces the attack of a struck opponent
Disarm skill has been acquired.
Disarm [Common Skill]
Temporarily reduces the attack of a struck opponent
Disarm temporarily lowers
my target's attack when I land a hit.
To be exact, it's 20% for one minute.
I need this skill to beat the Ariandype.
Bring it, monkey spider!
I'll take you on!
Elymas?!
Disarm [Common Skill]
Temporarily reduces the attack of a struck opponent
Disarm temporarily lowers
my target's attack when I land a hit.
Disarm [Common Skill]
Temporarily reduces the attack of a struck opponent
To be exact, it's 20% for one minute.
Bring it, monkey spider!
I'll take you on!
It's high-risk, high-reward!
But nothing fires me up like this!
Come at me, Ariandype!
I know its attack patterns and reach.
I won't get hit that easily.
What is that?
Poison Beam
I'll eat this attack...
on purpose!
Elymas?
And then I'll use...
Disarm
Disarm!
It barely made a dent,
but the attack debuff should've applied.
Flaming Claw
Oh, shit!
Elymas!
That won't work.
Poison Beam costs 7MP.
Flaming Claw costs 5MP.
Disarm
Disarm!
A second Disarm.
That's a 40% attack reduction.
And my title, Unwavering One, buffs my
defense by 10% when I'm holding position.
+10% Defense
when holding position
Okay, I'm ready.
Level and ability differences
can be overcome with knowledge.
Victory is mine!
Huh? What?!
Rampart Reflection!
Rampart Reflection
Hey!
Now it's over.
Level 12 reached.
4 skill points acquired
Four skill points have been acquired.
Additional points cannot be added
to Oath of the Heavy Armor at this time.
I recognize this message.
Of course.
So that Magic World
feature made it here, too.
Oath of the Heavy Armor reached level 15
Parry skill acquired
Oath of the Heavy Armor
has reached level 15.
Parry skill has been acquired.
But now, I've got my basic skills.
S-Seriously, who are you?
You probably could go it alone.
I shouldn't have been worried about you.
Sorry, I guess.
Hey, wait! You're poisoned!
Status effect: poisoned.
Status Effect
Poisoned
I'll escort you to town.
Thanks, Arus.
Even I can do that much.
Sorry.
Seriously, you saved me.
If we meet again,
I hope we'll still be friends.
Take care.
Father, please calm down.
It has the highest HP and defense.
I don't care about that!
Rampart Reflection!
Rampart Reflection
I always thought Elymas couldn't
bear the burden of being your heir.
The day after I beat the Ariandype,
I came to the Rondalm Adventurer's Guild
to register as an adventurer.
I'd like to register
as an adventurer, please.
My name is Elymas.
I'm level 12. My class is Heavy Knight.
Just a Heavy Knight?
Shouldn't have paid him any attention.
Heavy Knight is just another way
to say useless, right?
I see. You're a defensive class.
Understood.
F-rank adventurer Elymas approved.
F-rank
Elymas
Approved
Now I'm a proper adventurer.
S-rank
A-rank
B-rank
C-rank
There are seven adventurer ranks.
D-rank
Entering a dungeon requires at least
E-rank adventurers in the party.
E-rank
F-rank
Additional points cannot be added
to Oath of the Heavy Armor at this time.
Oath of the Heavy Armor
And rank limits the number of skill points
I can add to Oath of the Heavy Armor.
I need to reach E-rank ASAP.
Oh, also...
Hey, look.
Is that low-level Heavy Knight
looking for a party?
Who'd party with that trash?
Is anyone looking for a party?
Not many parties are looking for
shield users, so it may take some time.
I see.
I'm sorry.
Then I'll think about
joining a party at a later date.
For now...
This Magic Bag can store lots of items.
I'm glad I was able to take this.
I'd like to exchange my Magic Stones.
What is that?
Y-You gathered all of these yourself?
Yeah, I farmed them alone.
Put that in your report.
Huh? Um, okay.
He's not lying, right?
What's up with that Heavy Knight?
He must be cheating.
I've finished registering, and I've got
funds to cover living expenses.
What comes next gets my
Magic World player blood pumping!
Are there any promotion quests I can take?
What?!
I mean, technically, yes...
I heard a clown
had joined this Raid Quest.
It must be you, Elymas.
There are plenty of newbies like you
who underestimate guilds and monsters.
You beat an Ariandype at level 12?
Don't be stupid!
Adventuring isn't that easy!
I'll teach you a lesson!
Well, this sucks.
Translator:
Sho Stifler
Timer:
Krzysztof Kunc
Editor:
Salem Alabanza
Quality Control:
Gabriella Alabanza
Final Quality Control:
Sriram Gurunathan
I joined a Raid Quest
to raise my adventurer rank.
Ranks are tied to advancement caps.
But I've got a bad feeling
about this Raid Quest.
The arrogance of experienced
adventurers. Cowering newbies.
I hope nothing happens.
Next time, "The Raid Quest."
If we back each other up,
we have nothing to fear.